♪The spring breeze outside the window moves the stream♪
نسيم الربيع خارج النافذة يحرك التيار ♪
♪Who is disturbed by the williow catkins?♪
من ينزعج من طيور الصفصاف؟
♪You're there when I look back, toying with my heart♪
♪ أنت هناك عندما أنظر إلى الوراء ، ألعب بقلبي
♪Everything has become an ornament♪
كل شيء أصبح زخرفة ♪
♪A pair of lovebirds are flying under the roof in the drizzling rain♪
♪ زوج من طيور الحب تحلق تحت السقف تحت المطر المتساقط
♪Whose secrets have drifted to the chamber?♪
أسرار من انجرفت إلى الغرفة؟ ♪
♪The night when the moon shines, I'll have a drink with you♪
♪ في الليلة التي يشرق فيها القمر ، سأشرب معك
♪Let's keep each other company for the rest of our lifes♪
♪ لنحتفظ ببعضنا البعض لبقية حياتنا
♪The mountain and water carry me through my lifetime relationship♪
الجبل والماء يحملني عبر علاقة حياتي ♪
♪Oh, wind and rain, you're as romantic as spring♪
♪ أوه ، الرياح والمطر ، أنت رومانسي مثل الربيع ♪
♪Like the star and the moon, I wish you all well♪
♪ كالنجم والقمر أتمنى لكم كل خير ♪
♪Don't think about him, I'm right by your side♪
♪ لا تفكر فيه ، أنا بجانبك على حق
♪Oh, my dream keeps changing because of you♪
♪ أوه ، حلمي يتغير بسببك
♪I'm still waiting for you to look at me♪
♪ ما زلت أنتظر منك أن تنظر إلي ♪
♪It's hard to let go once one falls in love♪
♪ من الصعب التخلي عنها بمجرد أن يقع المرء في الحب
♪My life is not wasted while being with you♪
لا تضيع حياتي وأنا معك ♪
=Choice Husband=
= اختيار الزوج =
=Episode 20=
= الحلقة 20 =
As Pei Yanzhen predicted,
كما توقع Pei Yanzhen ،
they faked their death.
زيفوا موتهم.
But when they were buried,
ولكن عندما دفنوا ،
we had checked on them.
لقد فحصناها.
I heard there's a secret medicine in the Western Regions
سمعت أن هناك دواء سري في المناطق الغربية
that can stop one from breathing.
يمكن أن يمنع المرء من التنفس.
I guess this is the thing.
أعتقد أن هذا هو الشيء.
It looks like Shen Miao is
يبدو أن شين مياو
hiding something.
يخفي شيئا ما.
Miao,
مياو
you haven't eaten or drunk for three days.
لم تأكل أو تشرب لمدة ثلاثة أيام.
Have some food.
تناول بعض الطعام.
Where did you take Lvying?
اين اخذت Lvying؟
Try the fish congee I made.
جرب كونجي السمك الذي صنعته.
It's fragrant and soft.
إنه عبق وناعم.
It took me two hours to make it.
استغرق الأمر مني ساعتين لتحقيق ذلك.
Pei Yanzhen,
بي يانتشن ،
what are you trying to do?
ماذا تحاول أن تفعل؟
Miao,
مياو
you promised that you'll never leave me.
لقد وعدت أنك لن تتركني أبدًا.
You promised me that.
لقد وعدتني بذلك.
I was just spitballing and you really bought it.
لقد كنت مجرد spitballing وقمت بشرائه حقًا.
You're too naive, Your Highness.
أنت ساذج جدا يا صاحب السمو.
I just took a trip to the capital.
لقد قمت للتو برحلة إلى العاصمة.
What exactly has happened between us?
ما الذي حدث بالضبط بيننا؟
Just give Lvying back to me.
فقط أعيدوا Lvying لي.
Or else,
او اخرى،
I'll perish with you.
سوف أموت معك.
It seems like you're certain
يبدو أنك متأكد
that people from the Shen family have escaped.
أن أفراد عائلة شين قد هربوا.
Today, my subordinates came to report
اليوم ، أتى مرؤوسي للإبلاغ
that the coffins at the Shen's cemetery were forced open.
أن توابيت مقبرة شين أُجبرت على الفتح.
The bodies of your aunt and Shen Zai were missing.
كانت جثث عمتك وشين زاي مفقودة.
A lot of valuable stuff disappeared as well.
كما اختفى الكثير من الأشياء القيمة.
You've thought too much.
لقد فكرت كثيرًا.
Not everyone
ليس الجميع
in this world is as scheming as you.
في هذا العالم مكيدة مثلك.
But everyone in this world is
لكن كل شخص في هذا العالم
eyeing the fortune of the Shen family.
تتطلع إلى ثروة عائلة شين.
The tomb raiders are everywhere.
غزاة القبور في كل مكان.
So I'm sure this is the doing of the tomb raiders.
لذلك أنا متأكد من أن هذا من فعل غزاة القبور.
What has it got to do with me?
ما علاقة بي؟
I've heard of tomb raiding.
لقد سمعت عن مداهمة القبور.
But I didn't know they'd steal the bodies too.
لكنني لم أكن أعلم أنهم سرقوا الجثث أيضًا.
What's so surprising about it?
ما الذي يثير الدهشة في ذلك؟
Didn't you also keep my body
ألم تحتفظ بجسدي أيضًا
for three days?
لمدة ثلاثة أيام؟
Miao,
مياو
it's a big world.
إنه عالم كبير.
Unless Father-in-law can vanish into thin air,
ما لم يستطع والد الزوج أن يتلاشى في الهواء ،
otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
I'll certainly find them out
سأجدهم بالتأكيد
as long as I want.
طالما أردت.
Are you threatening me?
هل تهددنى؟
I'll get you another bowl of fish congee.
سأحضر لك وعاء آخر من سمك كونجي.
I've already got someone on my mind.
لدي بالفعل شخص ما في ذهني.
As long as I can watch her from afar,
طالما يمكنني مشاهدتها من بعيد ،
that'd be enough.
هذا سيكون كافيا.
Shut up.
اخرس.
Is this the young lady of the Shen family?
هل هذه السيدة الشابة لعائلة شين؟
She's so cute and smart.
انها لطيفة جدا وذكية.
I can tell that she's a beauty.
استطيع ان اقول انها جميلة.
Right.
حق.
When she turns sixteen,
عندما تبلغ السادسة عشرة من عمرها ،
I'm sure there'll be
أنا متأكد من أنه سيكون هناك
many young men asking to marry her.
يطلب الكثير من الشباب الزواج منها.
I agree.
أنا موافق.
She's still a kid.
إنها لا تزال طفلة.
Everything is not known yet.
كل شيء لم يعرف بعد.
Please take a seat over there.
من فضلك اجلس هناك.
Dad,
أب،
everyone compliments me.
الجميع يكملني.
Don't ever call me Hairless Girl again.
لا تدعوني فتاة بلا شعر مرة أخرى.
Look, you have sparse hair
انظري ، لديك شعر متناثر
that can't even be braided.
لا يمكن حتى مضفر.
It can only be made into a small bun.
لا يمكن تحويله إلا إلى كعكة صغيرة.
You're definitely
أنت بالتأكيد
Hairless Girl.
فتاة بلا شعر.
Everyone says this.
الجميع يقول هذا.
Don't you underestimate me.
لا تستهين بي.
It's not that you're beautiful.
ليس الأمر أنك جميلة.
Obviously, they only think that the fortune of
من الواضح أنهم يعتقدون فقط أن ثروة
the Shen family and your grandpa, the Lu family, is beautiful.
عائلة شين وجدك ، عائلة لو ، جميلة.
Miao, remember this.
مياو ، تذكر هذا.
As one of the Shen family,
كأحد أفراد عائلة شين ،
don't ever think of competing with the money.
لا تفكر أبدًا في التنافس مع المال.
To the people, money always comes
يأتي المال دائما للشعب
before the Shen family.
قبل عائلة شين.
Got it?
فهمتك؟
Good girl.
فتاة جيدة.
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
I've always remembered this.
لطالما تذكرت هذا.
How could I totally forgot about this
كيف يمكن أن أنسى هذا تماما
just because Pei Yanzhen rejected the proposal in front of everyone?
فقط لأن باي يانتشن رفض الاقتراح أمام الجميع؟
That I even dared to compare myself with the money.
حتى أنني تجرأت على مقارنة نفسي بالمال.
Well, now.
حسنآ الان.
I invited the bad guy over
دعوت الرجل السيئ
and lost all money the Shen family owned.
وخسرت كل الأموال التي تملكها عائلة شين.
Miao,
مياو
come and eat something.
تعال وكل شيئاً.
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
Eat with me.
كل معي.
After the meal,
بعد الوجبه،
I'll take you to Lvying.
سآخذك إلى Lvying.
You mean
أنت تعني
Mother has been sent to the mausoleum?
أم تم إرسال الأم إلى الضريح؟
And Pei Yanzhen
وباي يانتشن
is actually my...
هو في الواقع ...
His Majesty didn't tell you this
جلالة الملك لم يخبرك بهذا
because he didn't want to get you into this mess.
لأنه لا يريد أن يوقعك في هذه الفوضى.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
my martial brother isn't what you think he is.
أخي العسكري ليس كما تعتقد هو.
Besides, Shen Miao is alive and well now.
الى جانب ذلك ، شين مياو على قيد الحياة وبصحة جيدة الآن.
Just stop...
توقف...
What do you mean
ماذا تقصد
by the person I think he is?
من قبل الشخص الذي أعتقد أنه هو؟
He evicted
طرد
my mother.
أمي.
But the entire family of
لكن جميع أفراد عائلة
Pei Yanzhen's biological mother was killed.
قُتلت والدة باي يانتشن البيولوجية.
Now, even his foster parents
الآن ، حتى والديه بالتبني
were killed by Empress Dowager.
قُتلت على يد الإمبراطورة الأرملة.
I...
أنا...
Fine.
بخير.
Let me ask you this.
دعني أسألك هذا.
Did the Shen family
هل عائلة شين
have something to do with his family vendetta?
له علاقة بثأر عائلته؟
Did they kill his family?
هل قتلوا عائلته؟
No matter what,
بغض النظر،
I swear
أقسم
to be at daggers drawn with Pei Yanzhen.
لتكون في الخناجر المرسومة مع باي يانتشن.
Zhan Yue,
زان يو ،
if you take his side,
إذا أخذته إلى جانبه ،
from now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
let's not meet again.
دعونا لا نتقابل مرة أخرى.
Very well.
ممتاز.
Lvying.
ليفينغ.
Miss, are you alright?
آنسة ، هل أنت بخير؟
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Miaomiao,
مياومياو ،
did Pei Yanzhen make things hard for you?
هل جعل Pei Yanzhen الأمور صعبة عليك؟
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Did he threaten you by torturing you?
هل هددك بتعذيبك؟
I'll go to him now.
سأذهب إليه الآن.
Third Master,
السيد الثالث ،
let bygones be bygones.
اترك الماضي للماضي.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
you've helped me this time.
لقد ساعدتني هذه المرة.
I'll be sure to find a way to get you out of here.
سأكون على يقين من أن أجد طريقة لإخراجك من هنا.
What are you going to do?
ماالذي ستفعله؟
Are you going to curry favor with Pei Yanzhen?
هل ستتمتع بالرضا مع باي يانتشن؟
No way.
مستحيل.
I don't agree.
أنا لا أوافق.
No matter what,
بغض النظر،
it should be me to protect you.
يجب أن أكون أنا لحمايتك.
Miaomiao,
مياومياو ،
what exactly is going on?
ما الذي يحدث بالضبط؟
Is there any misunderstanding between us?
هل يوجد سوء تفاهم بيننا؟
If yes,
اذا نعم،
it must be Pei Yanzhen
يجب أن يكون باي يانتشن
who deliberately sows discord among us.
الذي يبث الشقاق بيننا عمدا.
The sun and moon can prove my love for you.
يمكن للشمس والقمر إثبات حبي لك.
Then, you tell me.
ثم أخبرني.
How did Pei Yanzhen make himself the Regent?
كيف جعل باي يانتشن نفسه وصيًا على العرش؟
In fact, just like you,
في الحقيقة ، مثلك تمامًا ،
I was deceived.
لقد خدعت.
Did Pei Yanzhen
هل بى يانتشن
incite you to marry me?
تحرضك على الزواج مني؟
No matter how our relationship started,
بغض النظر عن كيف بدأت علاقتنا ،
at this moment,
بهذه اللحظة،
I mean every word I say
أعني كل كلمة أقولها
and every move I make.
وكل حركة أقوم بها.
You haven't slept for three days.
أنت لم تنم لمدة ثلاثة أيام.
Go take a break.
اذهب وخذ قسط من الراحة.
No.
رقم.
There are some memorials I need to read.
هناك بعض النصب التذكارية التي يجب أن أقرأها.
Pei Yanzhen,
بي يانتشن ،
now that you've got your revenge,
الآن بعد أن حصلت على الانتقام ،
it's time for you to stop this.
حان الوقت لتوقف هذا.
You're asking me
أنت تسألني
to let go of Shen Miao?
لترك شين مياو؟
The Shen family faked their death,
زيفت عائلة شين موتهم ،
but it's true that you've used her.
لكن من الصحيح أنك استخدمتها.
There's a huge
هناك ضخمة
misunderstanding between you.
سوء تفاهم بينكما.
Miao.
مياو.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
I've got something to tell you.
أنا عندي شيء أقوله لك.
Will you let me hug you for a while?
هل تسمح لي أن أحضنك لبعض الوقت؟
Miao.
مياو.
You have no idea what has happened to me lately.
ليس لديك فكرة عما حدث لي مؤخرًا.
The imperial court is tumultuous.
البلاط الإمبراطوري صاخب.
My parents were forced to kill themselves.
أُجبر والداي على الانتحار.
Even you want to leave now.
حتى تريد المغادرة الآن.
If I could end this furor sooner,
إذا كان بإمكاني إنهاء هذا الغضب عاجلاً ،
maybe everything would be different.
ربما كل شيء سيكون مختلفا.
Miao,
مياو
don't ever leave me again, okay?
لا تتركني مرة أخرى ، حسنًا؟
Okay.
تمام.
If I promise you,
إذا وعدتك ،
when are you going to let Song Xiyuan go?
متى ستطلق سراح Song Xiyuan؟
Do you succumb to me
هل تستسلم لي
just to intercede for Song Xiyuan?
فقط للتوسط من أجل Song Xiyuan؟
If you don't let him go,
إذا لم تسمح له بالذهاب ،
- I'll... - What will you do?
- سوف ... - ماذا ستفعل؟
I'm just a commoner.
أنا مجرد عامة.
How would I dare
كيف أجرؤ
and how else can I do?
وكيف يمكنني أن أفعل؟
Are you going to talk to me like this?
هل ستتحدث معي هكذا؟
What else can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
You said that Shen family might be annihilated yourself.
لقد قلت أن عائلة شين قد تُبيد بنفسك.
I thought
اعتقدت
there might be some kind of mistake.
قد يكون هناك نوع من الخطأ.
It's like what you said.
إنه مثل ما قلته.
You use the sword with your left hand
تستخدم السيف بيدك اليسرى
and write with your right hand.
واكتب بيدك اليمنى.
You indeed excel in literature and martial arts.
أنت بالفعل تتفوق في الأدب وفنون الدفاع عن النفس.
No wonder you never used your left hand
لا عجب أنك لم تستخدم يدك اليسرى أبدًا
to hold my hand.
لعقد يدي.
Might be annihilated?
قد يُباد؟
Might be annihilated!
قد يُباد!
Pei Yanzhen,
بي يانتشن ،
that's so cruel of you.
هذا قاس جدا منك.
Listen to me, Miao.
استمع إلي يا مياو.
I can't believe you want to kill me
لا أصدق أنك تريد قتلي
with the hairpin I gave you.
مع دبوس الشعر الذي أعطيته لك.
I should've killed you earlier.
كان يجب أن أقتلك في وقت سابق.
It's the only way
انها الطريقة الوحيدة
to keep my family away from bad luck.
لإبعاد عائلتي عن سوء الحظ.
to take away my wrath.
لأخذ غضبي.
I can only take Xiao away after killing you.
لا يمكنني أخذ شياو بعيدًا إلا بعد قتلك.
So you faked your death
لذلك زورت موتك
just to get away from me
لمجرد الابتعاد عني
and find a chance to take revenge on me.
وتجد فرصة للانتقام مني.
So what if it's true?
إذن ماذا لو كان هذا صحيحًا؟
After what you did to the Shen family
بعد ما فعلته لعائلة شين
and me,
و أنا،
shouldn't I kill you?
الا يجب ان اقتلك
Shen Miao!
شين مياو!
You don't have to remind me
ليس عليك تذكيري
that my surname is Shen.
أن لقبي هو شين.
If not,
ان لم،
why would you marry me
لماذا تتزوجني
and feed me the contraceptive medicine?
ويطعمني دواء منع الحمل؟
If I wasn't from the Shen family,
إذا لم أكن من عائلة شين ،
why would you eagerly instruct the Song family to ask for my hand?
لماذا تطلب بشغف من عائلة سونغ أن تطلب يدي؟
It's just you feared that someone would obtain my family's fortune.
أنت فقط تخشى أن يحصل شخص ما على ثروة عائلتي.
Yet, you pretended to be at daggers drawn with them.
ومع ذلك ، فقد تظاهرت بأنك في خناجر مرسومة معهم.
If I wasn't from the Shen family,
إذا لم أكن من عائلة شين ،
why would you send Xiao to Pei's Residence
لماذا ترسل شياو إلى سكن باي
on the eve of your trip to the capital?
عشية رحلتك إلى العاصمة؟
It was to protect your son from getting hurt,
كان من أجل حماية ابنك من الأذى ،
when the Shen family was encircled and vanquished.
عندما حوصرت عائلة شين وقُهرت.
If I wasn't from the Shen family,
إذا لم أكن من عائلة شين ،
why would you put your life at stake
لماذا تضع حياتك على المحك
to reject the proposal?
لرفض الاقتراح؟
It was to cheat my dad out of his seal
كان لخداع والدي لإخراج ختمه
to help you with the regime change.
لمساعدتك في تغيير النظام.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
were you excited
هل انت متحمس
when you knew that I fell for you?
عندما علمت أني وقعت في حبك؟
The name "Pei Yanzhen" holds
يحمل اسم "Pei Yanzhen"
the meaning of concealing the truth.
معنى إخفاء الحقيقة.
I, Shen Miao, am really pathetic and ludicrous.
أنا ، شين مياو ، مثير للشفقة ومضحك حقًا.
I've lost my body, fortune and family
لقد فقدت جسدي وثروتي وعائلتي
for nothing.
من أجل لا شيء.
Even now, I still don't know about your real name.
حتى الآن ، ما زلت لا أعرف اسمك الحقيقي.
I'm such a joke,
يا لها من مزحة ،
that it's unprecedented.
هذا غير مسبوق.
It's extremely ridiculous.
إنه أمر سخيف للغاية.
So you think
هكذا تعتقد
that I incited Song Xiyuan to ask for your hand?
أنني حرضت Song Xiyuan على طلب يدك؟
I rejected the proposal
لقد رفضت الاقتراح
just to obtain the Shen family's seal?
فقط للحصول على ختم عائلة شين؟
Now that you've wielded wide powers,
الآن بعد أن مارست قوى واسعة ،
why bother pretending?
لماذا تهتم بالتظاهر؟
Didn't you marry me
ألم تتزوجيني
for the fortune of the Shen family?
من أجل ثروة عائلة شين؟
And for the Lu family's fortune?
ومن أجل ثروة عائلة لو؟
The whereabout of the Lu family's fortune is unknown.
مكان ثروة عائلة لو غير معروف.
You pull this charade
أنت تسحب هذه التمثيلية
just to make me talk.
فقط لأجعلني أتحدث.
Am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
It doesn't matter anymore.
لا يهم بعد الآن.
All I wish now is that you could let me go.
كل ما أتمناه الآن هو أن تدعني أذهب.
For the sake that the great fortune
من أجل هذا الثروة العظيمة
of the Shen family is within your reach.
من عائلة شين في متناول يدك.
And for the sake
ولأجل ذلك
that I've served you and your subordinate,
أنني خدمتك أنت ومرؤوسيك ،
Song Xiyuan
سونغ شيوان
for the past three years.
على مدى السنوات الثلاث الماضية.
Shut up!
اخرس!
Shen Miao,
شين مياو
I don't care what you think.
لا يهمني ما هو رأيك.
You've promised that you won't leave me.
لقد وعدت أنك لن تتركني.
You must practice
يجب أن تتدرب
what you preach.
ماذا تعظ.
(Without my command,)
(بدون إمرتي)
(Miss Shen is not allowed to leave here.)
(لا يُسمح الآنسة شين بالمغادرة هنا).
(Noted.)
(وأشار.)
(Shen's Residence)
(سكن شين)
Move!
يتحرك!
Be gentle.
كن لطيفآ.
Are you alright, Young Master?
هل أنت بخير أيها السيد الصغير؟
This is an order from His Highness.
هذا أمر من سموه.
Official Song, please leave Shen's Residence
الأغنية الرسمية ، من فضلك غادر Shen's Residence
and don't ever come back.
ولا تعود ابدا.
Young Master,
المعلم الصغير،
what should we do next?
ماذا علينا أن نفعل بعد ذلك؟
Let's go back to the capital.
دعنا نعود إلى العاصمة.
Pei Yanzhen holds great power now.
يتمتع Pei Yanzhen بقوة كبيرة الآن.
If we want to save Miaomiao from him,
إذا أردنا إنقاذ مياومياو منه ،
we'll have to make a well-thought-out plan.
سيتعين علينا وضع خطة مدروسة جيدًا.
Young Master,
المعلم الصغير،
are you sure you can defeat him?
هل أنت متأكد أنك تستطيع هزيمته؟
I'm serious
أنا جادة
this time.
هذا الوقت.
I've let Lvying in.
لقد تركت Lvying في.
I didn't tell her that it was your order.
لم أخبرها أنه طلبك.
Can't you two just talk nicely?
ألا يمكنكما التحدث بلطف؟
So what if I do?
إذن ماذا لو فعلت؟
Whatever I say now,
مهما قلته الآن ،
she won't believe it.
لن تصدق ذلك.
Dad.
أب.
Mom.
أم.
(Miao.)
(مياو.)
(You must stay safe.)
(يجب أن تظل آمنًا.)
Come take a look.
تعال والق نظرة.
Sir,
سيد،
did you return from the South?
هل عدت من الجنوب
I'd like to ask you something.
أود أن أسألك شيئا.
The South?
الجنوب؟
We can't go there anymore.
لا يمكننا الذهاب إلى هناك بعد الآن.
Now the national affairs are at Regent's command.
الآن الشؤون الوطنية تحت قيادة ريجنت.
He commanded to conduct strict investigations at the checkpoints.
وأمر بإجراء تحقيقات صارمة على الحواجز.
No one does business there anymore.
لا أحد يعمل هناك بعد الآن.
Regent?
ريجنت؟
He's the former Minister of Revenue,
إنه وزير الإيرادات السابق ،
Official Pei Yanzhen.
الرسمية باي يانتشن.
I'll get going.
سأذهب.
Please rise.
الرجاء النهوض.
I take refuge in the ancestral hall,
لقد لجأت إلى قاعة الأجداد ،
and ignore the public affairs.
وتجاهل الشأن العام.
Xiyuan, what do you need
Xiyuan ، ماذا تحتاج
to see me about?
لرؤيتي؟
I'm not here
انا لست هنا
for the public affairs.
للشؤون العامة.
I'm just wondering if you're keeping
أنا فقط أتساءل عما إذا كنت تحتفظ
a carp or a golden dragon in the pond.
شبوط أو تنين ذهبي في البركة.
You must be joking.
لابد أنك تمزح.
This is just a small garden.
هذه مجرد حديقة صغيرة.
There's no golden dragon.
لا يوجد تنين ذهبي.
A dragon should be staying at an abyss.
يجب أن يبقى التنين في الهاوية.
It lays dormant temporarily
يبقى كامنا مؤقتا
for the future.
للمستقبل.
Unfortunately,
للأسف،
the only golden dragon in the world
التنين الذهبي الوحيد في العالم
seems to have taken a long break
يبدو أنه قد أخذ استراحة طويلة
that its claws and scales have been worn blunt.
أن مخالبها ومقاييسها قد تآكلت بشكل حاد.
Nonsense!
كلام فارغ!
With Regent around,
مع ريجنت حولها ،
how dare you say that.
كيف تجرؤ على أن تقول ذلك.
I just want you to know
أنا فقط اريد منك ان تعرف
that whenever it is,
أنه كلما كان ،
I won't show my loyalty to anybody else
لن أُظهر ولائي لأي شخص آخر
besides Your Majesty.
بجانب جلالتك.
I'm tired.
أنا متعب.
You should go back.
يجب عليك العودة.
Young Master,
المعلم الصغير،
how was it?
كيف وجدته؟
His Majesty didn't agree.
جلالة الملك لم يوافق.
What to do, then?
ماذا تفعل إذن؟
Tie Niu,
التعادل نيو ،
look at the people behind me.
انظر إلى الأشخاص الذين ورائي.
Don't they look familiar?
ألا تبدو مألوفة؟
Young Master,
المعلم الصغير،
are you joking?
هل تمزح؟
This is my first time at the palace.
هذه هي المرة الأولى لي في القصر.
You're joking.
أنت تمزح.
Didn't you see them wearing
ألم تراهم يرتدون
the same military uniform as Pei Yanzhen's men?
نفس الزي العسكري لرجال باي يانتشن؟
We're toast.
نحن نخب.
Young Master,
المعلم الصغير،
you're saying
أنت تقول
that the entire palace has been under Pei Yanzhen's control?
أن القصر بأكمله كان تحت سيطرة باي يانتشن؟
It seems like I've underestimated him.
يبدو أنني قللت من شأنه.
He's able to go this far.
إنه قادر على الذهاب إلى هذا الحد.
I think it's just his choice
أعتقد أنه مجرد اختياره
whether to take the throne.
سواء أخذ العرش.
Doesn't it mean we're in great trouble now?
ألا يعني هذا أننا في ورطة كبيرة الآن؟
We're screwed.
لقد اخفقنا.
How could I have a silly subordinate like you?
كيف لي أن يكون لي مرؤوس سخيف مثلك؟
It doesn't mean
لا يعني ذلك
this will last forever.
هذا سوف يستمر إلى الأبد.
Pei Yanzhen is not in the capital.
بي يانتشن ليس في العاصمة.
Someone in court must've been restless.
يجب أن يكون شخص ما في المحكمة مضطربًا.
It's a perfect time to make connections.
إنه وقت مثالي لإجراء الاتصالات.
Come, Young Master.
تعال أيها السيد الشاب.
Miss.
يفتقد.
How could you have the mood
كيف يمكن أن يكون لديك الحالة المزاجية
to play with the bird at a time like this?
للعب مع الطائر في وقت مثل هذا؟
If it wasn't for it,
إذا لم يكن من أجلها ،
I'm afraid I would've died long ago.
أخشى أن أموت منذ فترة طويلة.
Also,
ايضا،
besides playing with the bird,
بجانب اللعب مع الطائر ،
what else can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
Miss Shen,
آنسة شين ،
His Highness asked me to bring the bird over.
طلب مني سموه إحضار الطائر.
Official Zhan,
زان الرسمية ،
this is the only fun Miss has got.
هذه هي المتعة الوحيدة التي حصلت عليها الآنسة.
This is His Highness's order.
هذا أمر سموه.
I dare not disobey it.
لا أجرؤ على عصيانه.
Miss.
يفتقد.
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
Guard Zhan,
الحرس زان ،
the Mid-Autumn Festival is approaching.
مهرجان منتصف الخريف يقترب.
Last year at this time,
العام الماضي في هذا الوقت ،
there were many people gathering at Shen's Residence,
كان هناك الكثير من الناس يتجمعون في Shen's Residence ،
viewing the moon, enjoying mooncakes
مشاهدة القمر والاستمتاع بكعك القمر
and eating osmanthus cakes.
وأكل كعك الأوسمانثوس.
Everything is different now.
كل شيء مختلف الآن.
But I need to find sustenance in something.
لكني بحاجة إلى إيجاد القوت في شيء ما.
Can you please buy me some osmanthus cakes?
هل يمكنك شراء بعض كعكات الأوسمانثوس من فضلك؟
Pei Yanzhen, the scholar,
Pei Yanzhen ، الباحث ،
is handsome and knowledgeable.
وسيم وواسع المعرفة.
He's a decent gentleman.
إنه رجل محترم.
Do you really think
هل تعتقد حقا
this silly bird is a trap that Song Xiyuan set?
هذا الطائر السخيف هو الفخ الذي وضعه Song Xiyuan؟
Whether it's true or not,
سواء كان ذلك صحيحًا أم لا ،
I don't want it to stay by Miao's side.
لا أريد أن يبقى بجانب مياو.
I'll go get Shen Miao some pastries.
سأذهب لإحضار بعض المعجنات لشين مياو.
Pei
بي
is so mean.
لئيم جدا.
He'll be back soon?
هل سيعود قريبا؟
But he's not back yet.
لكنه لم يعد بعد.
Fried Cabbage with Vinegar.
ملفوف مقلي بالخل.
Pei Yanzhen,
بي يانتشن ،
are you captured by Empress Dowager?
هل تم أسرك من قبل الإمبراطورة الأرملة؟
Mother,
الأم،
can you stop disturbing me?
هل تستطيع التوقف عن مضايقتي؟
How can you talk to your mother like this?
كيف يمكنك التحدث مع والدتك مثل هذا؟
Great-uncle said
قال العم
one should concentrate,
يجب على المرء أن يركز ،
be sincere, be patient
كن مخلصا ، كن صبورا
and clear the mind while studying.
وتصفية الذهن أثناء الدراسة.
Let me see what you're reading.
دعني أرى ما تقرأه.
- Come on. - No.
- تعال.  - رقم.
Let me see.
دعنى ارى.
Or I'll tickle you.
أو سأدغدغك.
If you don't let me see,
إذا لم تدعني أرى ،
I'll tickle you.
سوف دغدغة لك.
Let me take a look.
دعني ألقي نظرة.
Do you know all these words?
هل تعرف كل هذه الكلمات؟
(Peace and Prosperity)
(السلام والازدهار)
Miss, here are the osmanthus cakes.
آنسة ، ها هي كعكات الأوسمانثوس.
Miss.
يفتقد.
What did Master Song say?
ماذا قال ماستر سونغ؟
Song Xiyuan said
قال سونغ شيوان
he has contacted
لقد اتصل
the officials in the capital who are against Pei Yanzhen.
المسؤولون في العاصمة الذين يعارضون باي يانتشن.
He asked us to find a way to go to the capital.
طلب منا إيجاد طريقة للذهاب إلى العاصمة.
Then, he'll take the chance to get us out.
بعد ذلك ، سوف ينتهز الفرصة لإخراجنا.
It looks like Master Song
يبدو مثل Master Song
is true to you, Miss.
هو صادق بالنسبة لك يا آنسة.
There are good guys in the world.
هناك رجال طيبون في العالم.
Then, do you think
ثم ، هل تعتقد
he does it for my sake
يفعل ذلك من أجلي
or for the sake of the Lu family's fortune?
أو من أجل ثروة عائلة لو؟
Do you know where the Lu family hid their money?
هل تعلم أين خبأت عائلة لو أموالهم؟
If we get the money,
إذا حصلنا على المال ،
would we be able to bring Regent down?
هل سنتمكن من إسقاط ريجنت؟
The Lu family's fortune is
ثروة عائلة لو
just a rumor.
مجرد شائعة.
But,
لكن،
we can use this method
يمكننا استخدام هذه الطريقة
to go to the capital.
للذهاب إلى العاصمة.
It takes forever to pick it like this.
يستغرق الأمر وقتًا طويلاً لاختياره بهذه الطريقة.
After so long,
بعد فترة طويلة،
it's all I've got.
كل ما لدي.
I got an idea.
حصلت على فكرة.
Lvying.
ليفينغ.
Lv...
مستوى ...
Pei Yanzhen,
بي يانتشن ،
come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Perfect timing.
توقيت ممتاز.
I'd like to make osmanthus cakes today.
أود أن أصنع كعك الأوسمانثوس اليوم.
Help me pick some osmanthus flowers, will you?
ساعدني في اختيار بعض زهور الأوسمانثوس ، أليس كذلك؟
You're so virtuous.
أنت فاضل جدا.
What can I do to repay you?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل لسداد لك؟
Just let me enjoy the food alone.
فقط دعني أستمتع بالطعام وحدي.
Just don't eat it.
فقط لا تأكله.
It's considered a payback.
إنه يعتبر ثمناً.
Will you help me?
هل ستساعدني؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
♪For whom am I waiting this relationship for?♪
♪ لمن أنتظر هذه العلاقة؟ ♪
♪The tangling love becomes the river under the sky♪
الحب المتشابك يصير النهر تحت السماء
♪The years are long. The night is short. The clear spring wine is warm♪
السنوات طويلة.  الليل قصير.  نبيذ الربيع الصافي دافئ ♪
♪The passing of time goes on and on♪
مرور الوقت يطول و يطرأ ♪
This will be sufficient.
سيكون هذا كافيا.
Quickly get down here.
انزل بسرعة إلى هنا.
Well,
نحن سوف،
Lvying took the ladder away.
أخذ Lvying السلم بعيدا.
She went to pick the flowers from another tree.
ذهبت لتقطف الزهور من شجرة أخرى.
Well, you can catch me from down there.
حسنًا ، يمكنك اللحاق بي من هناك.
I'll jump off the roof.
سأقفز من فوق السطح.
I only agreed to catch the flowers for you.
أنا فقط وافقت على التقاط الزهور من أجلك.
I didn't say I'd catch you.
أنا لم أقل أنني سأمسك بك.
Pei Yanzhen!
بي يانتشن!
Then, am I allowed to try the cake?
إذن ، هل يسمح لي بتجربة الكعكة؟
Lvying!
ليفينغ!
Lv...
مستوى ...
Pei Yanzhen,
بي يانتشن ،
you don't have compassion for the lady.
ليس لديك شفقة للسيدة.
Didn't you refuse
ألم ترفض
to help me?
لتساعدني؟
They are
هم انهم
different.
مختلف.
If you catch me,
إذا أمسكت بي ،
I'll make osmanthus cakes for you every year.
سأصنع كعكات الأوسمانثوس لك كل عام.
Miao.
مياو.
Be careful!
كن حذرا!
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Miao,
مياو
I'd like to eat the osmanthus cakes you make.
أود أن آكل كعك الأوسمانثوس الذي تصنعه.
You said
أنت قلت
that if I caught you,
أنه إذا أمسكت بك ،
you'd make osmanthus cakes for me every year.
كنت ستصنع كعكات الأوسمانثوس لي كل عام.
But the next year,
لكن في العام المقبل ،
we got divorced hastily.
طلقنا على عجل.
Now that I've caught you,
الآن بعد أن مسكتك ،
where is my osmanthus cake?
أين كعكة الأوسمانثوس خاصتي؟
I did make you osmanthus cakes.
لقد صنعت لك كعك أوسمانثوس.
Did you forget it?
هل نسيتها؟
Pei Yanzhen,
بي يانتشن ،
I even specially made you...
حتى أنني صنعتك خصيصًا ...
Miss Shen,
آنسة شين ،
I'm promoted to Minister of Revenue.
لقد تمت ترقيتي إلى وزير الدخل.
I'll leave Lingzhou and go to the capital with His Majesty
سأترك Lingzhou وأذهب إلى العاصمة مع جلالة الملك
tomorrow to take office.
غدا لتولي المنصب.
♪Grant me a life where we grow old together♪
♪ امنحني الحياة حيث نتقدم في العمر معًا ♪
♪Who sends the love letter while leaning at the railing♪
♪ من يرسل رسالة الحب وهو يميل على الدرابزين ♪
♪At the river of lovesickness?♪
عند نهر الغثيان؟
♪Grant me happiness for the rest of my life together with you♪
♪ امنحني السعادة لبقية حياتي معك
It was the osmanthus cake you made?
هل كانت كعكة الأوسمانثوس التي صنعتها؟
Did you not know what it was?
ألم تعرف ماذا كان؟
I never opened it.
لم أفتحه أبدًا.
Because I was afraid if I opened it,
لأنني كنت خائفًا إذا فتحته ،
I wouldn't have the heart
لن يكون لدي قلب
to leave you and our kid behind
لتركك أنت وولدنا خلفك
and go to the capital.
والذهاب إلى العاصمة.
That time, you said
قلت في ذلك الوقت
you didn't want to implicate us,
أنت لا تريد توريطنا ،
so you heartlessly rejected us
لذلك رفضتنا بلا قلب
and left us alone.
وتركنا وشأننا.
But now, you always claim
لكن الآن ، أنت تدعي دائمًا
that you keep me here
أن تبقيني هنا
and separate me from my kid
وتفصلني عن طفلي
for my own good.
لبلدي الخير الخاصة.
Pei Yanzhen,
بي يانتشن ،
I can't figure out
لا أستطيع معرفة ذلك
if you're telling me
إذا كنت تخبرني
the truth.
الحقيقة.
Miao,
مياو
the two things you mentioned
الشيئين اللذين ذكرتهما
are true.
صحيحة.
The moon is almost full.
القمر يكاد يكون كاملا.
Yanzhen,
يانتشن ،
I'm just an ordinary lady.
أنا مجرد سيدة عادية.
All I wish is a simple sheer of happiness.
كل ما أتمناه هو مجرد السعادة.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
let's stop harboring suspicion,
دعونا نتوقف عن إيواء الشك ،
and forget about the power
ونسيان القوة
and the fortune,
والثروة ،
okay?
حسنا؟
I'll overlook the past.
سأتغاضى عن الماضي.
It's the Mid-Autumn Festival.
إنه مهرجان منتصف الخريف.
Let's be happy together.
دعونا نكون سعداء معا.
I'll pick the osmanthus flowers
سأقطف زهور الأوسمانثوس
to make pastries for you every year.
لعمل المعجنات لك كل عام.
Okay?
تمام؟
What's done is done.
ما حدث قد حدث.
I've gone so far.
لقد ذهبت بعيدا.
I can't just give up as I want.
لا يمكنني الاستسلام كما أريد.
The entire world belongs to the Emperor.
العالم كله ملك للإمبراطور.
Only with the power,
فقط مع القوة ،
I can protect you and Xiao.
يمكنني حمايتك أنت وشياو.
You can't have it both ways.
لا يمكن استخدام الطريقتين.
The moon waxes only to wane. What goes up must come down.
القمر يشمع فقط ليختفي.  ما طار طير وارتفع إلا كما طار وقع.
Your Highness, you're too ambitious
صاحب السمو ، أنت طموح للغاية
and greedy.
والجشع.
It's not that I'm greedy.
ليس الأمر أنني جشع.
But this is the fact.
لكن هذه هي الحقيقة.
Miao,
مياو
just stay by my side
فقط ابقى بجانبي
and have faith in me.
ويؤمن بي.
Unfortunately,
للأسف،
even if you keep me here for my entire life,
حتى لو بقيتني هنا طوال حياتي ،
you still won't be able to get the fortune of the Shen and Lu family.
ما زلت غير قادر على الحصول على ثروة عائلة شين ولو.
The two families' fortune is no longer in my hands.
ثروة العائلتين لم تعد في يدي.
They're not with any of the Shen family either.
إنهم ليسوا مع أي من عائلة شين أيضًا.
I've already given it to somebody else.
لقد أعطيته بالفعل لشخص آخر.
(You still think that I do this for the Lu family's fortune?)
(هل ما زلت تعتقد أنني أفعل هذا من أجل ثروة عائلة لو؟)
Is it Song Xiyuan again?
هل هي Song Xiyuan مرة أخرى؟
Does it matter?
هل يهم؟
Just get some rest.
فقط خذ قسطا من الراحة.
I'll come and visit you again.
سآتي وأزورك مرة أخرى.
I'm too greedy.
أنا جشع جدا.
It's just a few pieces of osmanthus cakes.
إنها مجرد قطع قليلة من كعك الأوسمانثوس.
It's no match for the great fortune of the two families.
إنه لا يضاهي الثروة العظيمة للأسرتين.
Let alone the entire nation.
ناهيك عن الأمة بأكملها.
Regent invents new policies.
ريجنت يخترع سياسات جديدة.
He stops the mutiny, allows people to raise voices, combats corruption,
يوقف التمرد ، ويسمح للناس برفع الأصوات ، ويحارب الفساد ،
promotes agricultural development, reduces taxes, expands the imperial exam,
يعزز التنمية الزراعية ، ويقلل الضرائب ، ويوسع الامتحان الإمبراطوري ،
and rectifies the officials' styles of work.
ويصحح أساليب عمل المسؤولين.
We'll do as he commands.
سنفعل كما يأمر.
But now, the national treasury is empty.
لكن الآن ، الخزانة الوطنية فارغة.
If we reduce the taxes,
إذا قللنا الضرائب ،
we won't be able to support the soldiers who are posted at the border gate
لن نتمكن من دعم الجنود المنتشرين عند البوابة الحدودية
and it'll make things hard for the scholar and military officials.
وستجعل الأمور صعبة على الباحث والمسؤولين العسكريين.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
prohibit referrals, expand the imperial exam and recruit talents
حظر الإحالات وتوسيع الامتحان الإمبراطوري وتجنيد المواهب
might be able to prevent the officials from forming a conspiracy.
قد تكون قادرة على منع المسؤولين من تشكيل مؤامرة.
But it'll also cause the problem of having redundant officials.
لكنه سيسبب أيضًا مشكلة وجود موظفين فائضين عن الحاجة.
Do not make rash decisions.
لا تتخذ قرارات متهورة.
Liu,
ليو ،
you're the Minister of Personnel.
أنت وزير شؤون الموظفين.
Do not talk nonsense.
لا تتحدث بلا منطق.
Your Majesty,
جلالة الملك ،
this is not nonsense.
هذا ليس هراء.
Please reconsider it.
يرجى إعادة النظر فيه.
Regent has made up his mind.
ريجنت اتخذ قراره.
Do not cause trouble again.
لا تسبب المتاعب مرة أخرى.
Are you trying
هل تحاول
to make Regent mad?
لجعل ريجنت مجنون؟
That's enough.
هذا يكفي.
I'm tired.
أنا متعب.
Let's call it a day.
دعونا نسميها اليوم.
If there's anything else,
إذا كان هناك أي شيء آخر ،
just let Regent make the decision.
فقط دع ريجنت يتخذ القرار.
- Goodbye, Your Majesty.
- وداعا جلالة الملك.  - وداعا جلالة الملك.
As Regent insists
كما يصر ريجنت
on reducing taxes and rectifying the styles of work,
بشأن تخفيض الضرائب وتعديل أنماط العمل ،
we won't have the money, the guts and the time
لن نمتلك المال والشجاعة والوقت
to listen to music, enjoy dances and drink wine here anymore.
للاستماع إلى الموسيقى والاستمتاع بالرقصات وشرب الخمر هنا بعد الآن.
Official Lu, are you afraid of being annihilated?
المسؤول لو ، هل أنت خائف من أن تُباد؟
But isn't it too late to say this now?
لكن ألم يفت الأوان لقول هذا الآن؟
When you supported Official Pei back then,
عندما دعمت Official Pei في ذلك الوقت ،
did you ever think that this would happen?
هل فكرت يوما أن هذا سيحدث؟
Official Song,
الأغنية الرسمية ،
you're the only one
أنت الوحيد
who can confront him now.
من يستطيع مواجهته الآن.
Do you have a plan?
هل لديك خطة؟
Tie Niu.
التعادل نيو.
All of you may leave.
كل واحد منكم قد يغادر.
Since the Regent is unkind,
بما أن الوصي قاسٍ ،
we could just go against him.
يمكننا فقط الذهاب ضده.
Giving the power back to His Majesty
إعادة القوة إلى جلالة الملك
is the right thing to do.
هو الشيء الصحيح الذي ينبغي عمله.
But the military troop is under Pei Yanzhen's command.
لكن القوات العسكرية تخضع لقيادة باي يانتشن.
How are we supposed to do that?
كيف يفترض بنا أن نفعل ذلك؟
Eliminate his bodyguards,
القضاء على حراسه الشخصيين ،
lower his guard,
خفض حذره ،
and lure him into the trap.
وإغرائه في الفخ.
It'll make things a lot easier for us.
ستجعل الأمور أسهل كثيرًا بالنسبة لنا.
But there's no way he'd do it without a struggle.
لكن لا توجد طريقة لفعل ذلك بدون معاناة.
I have my way.
لدي طريقي.
He's here.
إنه هنا.
Miss!
يفتقد!
How is your foot?
كيف حال قدمك؟
Miao,
مياو
your arm has just recovered.
لقد تعافت ذراعك للتو.
How could you be so careless?
كيف يمكن أن تكون مهملا جدا؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
It's the Mid-Autumn Festival today.
إنه عيد منتصف الخريف اليوم.
But there's no one
لكن لا يوجد أحد
at Shen's Residence,
في Shen's Residence ،
and I'm all alone here.
وأنا وحيد هنا.
So I was a little spaced out.
لذلك كنت متباعدة قليلاً.
You have me.
انت معي.
I'm here with you.
أنا هنا معكم.
Miao,
مياو
what would you like to eat?
ماذا تريد أن تأكل؟
Or what would you like to watch?
أو ماذا تريد أن تشاهد؟
I'll have it arranged right away.
سوف أجعلها مرتبة على الفور.
I can do that too.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك أيضا.
Just that
هذا فقط
I'd like to go out and buy something.
أود الخروج وشراء شيء ما.
Do you allow me to do that?
هل تسمح لي بفعل ذلك؟
What do you need?
ماذا تحتاج؟
I'll ask someone to buy it for you.
سأطلب من شخص ما أن يشتريه لك.
It's the Mid-Autumn Festival today.
إنه عيد منتصف الخريف اليوم.
I'd like to make some osmanthus cakes as it's the tradition
أود صنع بعض كعك الأوسمانثوس لأنه التقليد
of the Shen family.
من عائلة شين.
But making osmanthus cakes
لكن صنع كعك أوسمانثوس
is quite an art. There are many things to pay attention to.
هو تماما فن.  هناك أشياء كثيرة يجب الانتباه إليها.
I'm afraid the servants won't know what I need.
أخشى أن الخدم لن يعرفوا ما أحتاجه.
But you just sprained your ankle.
لكنك لويت كاحلك للتو.
I'm alright.
أنا بخير.
Look.
نظرة.
It's doing well.
إنها تعمل بشكل جيد.
I'll ask Zhan Yue to go with you.
سأطلب من Zhan Yue الذهاب معك.
He can protect you.
يمكنه حمايتك.
Okay?
تمام؟
As you wish.
كما تتمنا.
Miao,
مياو
the osmanthus cakes for tonight,
كعك الأوسمانثوس الليلة ،
can I have them too?
هل يمكنني الحصول عليها أيضا؟
I'll see you here
سأراك هنا
tonight.
هذه الليلة.
♪There are many devoted lovers in the mortal world♪
هناك العديد من العشاق المخلصين في العالم الفاني
♪It's hard to understand love♪
♪ من الصعب أن تفهم الحب ♪
♪If I have another chance, I won't be late again♪
♪ إذا سنحت لي فرصة أخرى ، فلن أتأخر مرة أخرى
♪All I wish is for you to be well♪
♪ كل ما أتمناه هو أن تكوني بخير ♪
♪Don't ask me if this is worth it♪
♪ لا تسألني إذا كان هذا يستحق ذلك ♪
♪However, love is♪
لكن الحب هو ♪
♪Turning into lovesickness when it deepens into your heart♪
تتحول إلى غشاوة عندما تتعمق في قلبك
♪Even life and death can't frighten me♪
♪ حتى الحياة والموت لا يمكن أن يخيفاني
♪I've been through the good times and bad times♪
♪ لقد مررت بأوقات طيبة وأخرى سيئة ♪
♪But the person I've been waiting for is not aware of it♪
♪ لكن الشخص الذي كنت أنتظره ليس على علم بذلك
♪There's an unfinished story between you and me♪
♪ هناك قصة غير منتهية بيني وبينك
♪How am I supposed to continue my life?♪
♪ كيف لي أن أكمل حياتي؟
♪The moon rises and sets, a day has passed♪
القمر يطلع ويغيب مضى يوم ♪
♪I just want to protect you until old ages♪
♪ أريد فقط أن أحميك حتى الشيخوخة ♪
♪And make a vow about you♪
وأقطع نذرًا عنك
♪I'm willing to be obsessed with you♪
♪ أنا على استعداد لأن أكون مهووسًا بك ♪
♪I wish we could be together in our next lifes♪
♪ أتمنى أن نكون معًا في حياتنا القادمة